DUY **D**o

Artificial Intelligence Expert - AI Project Manager

linkedin.com/in/duydv ♦ doduy.github.io

Prof.	essional Summary
the world. Hands-on experience in big data/art	secially love new technologies that help solve real problems in ificial intelligence development. Solid experience in Machine
multivariable calculus. Research experience in good problem-solving skill. Personality: being	ekground about statistics, probabilities, linear algebra and various computer science fields. Highly logical thinking and hard-working, enthusiasm, carefulness, and a big will to learn. I ake a difference in a big way, always dream about making the
world it better place.	SKILLS —————
Data Analysis	
Data AnalysisComputer Vision, OCR	Deep Learning Framework: Tensorflow, KerasMachine Learning Library: scikit-learn
 Natural Language Processing 	 Program Language: python

AI Leader, 12/2018 to Current

Heligate – Me Tri, Ha Noi

• Design solutions and develop AI project focus on OCR for both handwriting and machine printed in English and Japanese

WORK HISTORY

- Pre-sales, research and write proposals for customers' needs
- Design and operate process for AI projects

AI Project Manager, 09/2019 to 05/2020

Heligate – Me Tri, Ha Noi

- Manage an AI team of All-Stars/ 5 members
- Research new opportunities in healthcare and others
- Report to CEO

Machine Learning Engineer, 06/2016 to 08/2018

FPT Software - Cau Giay, Ha Noi

- Research new techniques in AI to create PoCs to demonstrate the capabilities of FTP Software to customers.
- Joins FSoft's AI projects as an Engineer for computer vision problems.
- Develop training AI fundamental courses.

Researcher's Assistant, 01/2015 to 05/2016

University of Engineering and Technology VNUH - Cau Giay, Ha Noi

- Researched and created new algorithms using SAT to solve the Hitori logic problem.
- Collected data, developed programs that demonstrate the effectiveness of new algorithms.
- Participated the conference: Students with Scientific Research University of Engineering and Technology VNUH 2016

|--|--|

• Information Extraction

In this project I designed and developed an Engine could extract information in scanned documents from predefined categories

• Symbol Detection

I managed a team to develop a module could detect handwriting symbol in scanned documents

• Orientation Detection and Style of Word Classification

In this project I designed and developed 2 modules, one could detect orientation of scanned documents, one could classify Style of cropped text images (machine printed, handwriting,...)

• Japanese OCR Engine

I managed a team to develop an OCR Engine that could recognize both Japanese handwriting and machine printed text

• English OCR Engine

In this project I designed and developed an OCR Engine that could recognize both English handwriting and machine printed text

• Diseases Detection from Chest X-ray data

This is a personal project. I created the proposal, using a very new Kaggle dataset to implement this project. The project focuses on using techniques in deep learning to analyze X-ray image data and some of the patient's personal information to predict the disease.

The project uses Keras framework and main techniques used and compared are CNN and CapsNet, more details see on my Github page.

• Facial Recognition

Building facial recognition systems for FPT Software, my work is to research the latest facial recognition technology, consulting and implementing.

Using facial recognition technology to support and implement some projects with customers of FSoft units, check in the system for students entering class for a customer.

• Future Marketing

This is FSoft's internal project, building an Intelligent Marketing System using AI such as Customer segmentation, Social listening and so on.

Project management and implementation of AI cores section.

•	Udacity Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree, 2017 to 2018
•	Information Technology, 2012 to 2016 University of Engineering and Technology VNU - Cau Giay, Ha Noi
	————— Certifications —————

EDUCATION

- Deep Learning Specialization Deep Learning.ai, Coursera
- Machine Learning Engineer Nanodegree Udacity
- Machine Learning Stanford University, Coursera
- Introduction to Neurohacking In R Johns Hopkins University, Coursera
- Recommender Systems Specialization University of Minnesota, Coursera
- Data Engineering on Google Cloud Platform Specialization Google, Coursera
- Implementing RPA with Cognitive Automation and Analytics Specialization Automation Anywhere, Coursera